A Guide to the Margaret Fowler Clark Papers
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Margaret Fowler Clark Papers 1865-1980, n.d.
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
4702-d, -e, -f
This collection consists of ca. 336 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was gifted to the library on 1980 September 1, 1980 October 22, and 1980 December 12.
Contents List
- Town Hall-Levy Opera House Foundation: Constitution, Minutes, By-Laws, Agendas, etc. 1971-1977, n.d.
  24 items
- Town Hall-Levy Opera House Foundation: Correspondence 1968-1978, n.d.
  69 items
- Town Hall-Levy Opera House Foundation: Miscellaneous 1971-1976, n.d.
  16 items
- Newspaper Clippings re the Town Hall-Levy Opera House 1971-1975, n.d.
  31 items
- Historical sketches partially included in The Golden Age of the Performing Arts by Margaret Fowler Clark 1972, 1974-1978, n.d.
- Correspondence re The Golden Age of the Performing Arts by Margaret Fowler Clark 1976-1978
  32 items
- Photographs for The Golden Age of the Performing Arts by Margaret Fowler Clark 1975-1978, n.d.
  29 items
- The Golden Age of the Performing Arts by Margaret Fowler Clark 1976
  1 item
- Correspondence of Margaret Fowler Clark w/E.G. Swem 1954, 1957
  2 items
- Correspondence and notes re the Butler, Fowler, and Staples families and their properties 1954, 1968, 1974
  10 items
- Miscellaneous correspondence of Margaret Fowler Clark and material re the James River and Kanawah Canal and Ezra Pound 1942, 1968-1969, 1972
  8 items
- Armistead Deer Hunting Club of Virginia: Miscellaneous legal papers and photographs 1865, 1892, 1895, 1978
  6 items
- Joseph Jenkins Roberts, first president of Liberia: Research correspondence and notes 1949
  5 items
- Photographs of old homes in Charlottesville 1978
- Miscellaneous ca. 1900-1912, 1943, 1952, 1971-1979, n.d.
  14 items
- Notes re Civil War history, Midway School, Charlottesville, Virginia, and photographs of "Winton," the home of the mother of Patrick Henry and Judge Frank Campbell in Amherst County, Virginia (now the Amherst County Dining Club) 1973, 1980, n.d.
  13 items